Damien's prophecy is reborn!
Omen IV: The Awakening is a horror, mystery,
thriller film directed by Jorge Montesi.
Damien Thorn is dead, but his prophecy is reborn in a mysterious
girl named Delia, who is adopted by two attorneys.
Karen York, played by Faye Grant.
Gene York, played by Michael Woods.
Earl, played by Michael Lerner.
Dr. Hastings, played by Madison Mason.
Jo Thueson, played by Ann Hearn.
Noah, played by Jim Byrnes.
Omen IV: The Awakening is a 1991 American supernatural horror television film directed by Jorge Montesi and Dominique
Othenin-Girard and written by Brian Taggert, from a story by producer Harvey Bernhard and Taggert.
The film is the fourth installment in The Omen franchise and
the final installment of the original franchise.
It stars Faye Grant, Michael Woods, Michael Lerner, and Asia Vieira.
Its plot follows two attorneys who adopt a young girl, unaware of the fact
that she is to possibly succeed Damien Thorn as the Antichrist.
The film was intended to be the first of many television sequels to
20th Century Fox's film history of popular titles.
Bernhard, who also produced the previous three Omen films,
felt there could be more done to the series.
This was the last film he produced.
He previously wrote the story for the second film.
Omen IV: The Awakening premiered on television in North
America on the Fox network, on May 20, 1991.
The film was given a theatrical release in some countries, such as Australia, where it premiered on
August 9, 1991, and in the United Kingdom, where it opened on November 29, 1991.
It was largely panned by critics upon release.
The film explores themes of prophecy, politics,
anti-christ, evil child, mysterious death.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.